Disaster recovery, or DR,
灾难恢复或 DR
refers to worst-case scenarios.
是指最坏的情况
What do you do and how fast can you restore service after a major failure?
您做了什么以及在重大故障后恢复服务的速度有多快 ?
Well, RTO and RPO apply to any failure incident.
那么 RTO 和 RPO 适用于任何故障事件
What values you can commit to for your RTO and RPO?
您可以为 RTO 和 RPO 落实哪些值 ?
You need to consider these worst-case scenarios.
您需要考虑这些最坏情况
In a traditional data center,
在传统的数据中心中
this would be a complete failure of that data center.
这将是该数据中心的完全失败
Another example would be a major Internet outage.
另一个示例将是重大的因特网中断
How do you get your platform back online when the normal home
正常家居时如何让你的平台重新上线
for your platform looks like it'll be down for some significant period?
你的平台看起来会有一段很重要的时间吗
First of all, make sure you have everything that you need.
首先 确保您拥有所需的一切
What are those things?
那些东西是什么
Database backups, server images, your application code,
数据库备份 服务器映像 应用程序代码
server configurations, other data repositories,
服务器配置 其他数据存储库
network configuration, documentation, IP whitelist.
网络配置 文档  IP 白名单
Moving takes a lot of work and a lot of things and you can't forget anything.
搬家需要很多工作和很多事情 你不能忘记任何事情
If you forget something or have an old version of something,
如果你忘记了一些东西或者有个旧版本的东西
your DR cut over may take much longer or fail completely.
您的 DR 中断可能需要更长时间或完全失败
Remember, not only must all of your applications and data be available to move,
请记住 不仅必须提供所有应用程序和数据才能移动
but also your documentation.
还有你的证件
There are many things that can go wrong.
有很多事情是可以出错的
Documentation is a must and will be invaluable when you are performing a DR failover.
在执行 DR 故障转移时 文档是必须的 并且将非常有用
Keep in mind, this failover may have to be run by
请记住 此故障转移可能必须由
less experienced staff in the middle of the night under very stressful conditions.
在非常紧张的条件下 在午夜的时间里 很少有经验的工作人员
What can you do to make it success,
你能做些什么使它成功
not only possible but likely?
不仅可能而且很可能
Practice. Run through every step if possible and make
练习 如果可能 请执行每个步骤并进行
sure that the documentation is actually reflective of your platform.
确保文档实际反映了您的平台
Practice until you get it right,
练习直到你明白
practice until you no longer have to cheat,
直到你不再作弊
and go look at your current infrastructure
然后去看看你现在的基础设施
to make sure you've got all the pieces assembled correctly.
确保所有零件都组装好
Practice often. Things change over time,
经常练习 随着时间的推移
new features are released,
发布新功能
new services are utilized.
使用新服务
If you don't practice frequently,
如果你不经常练习
then you run the risk of realizing that you're DR documentation is out of date,
你就会冒险意识到自己的 DR 文档已经过时了
only when you're in the midst of a real DR event.
只有当你身处一个真正的 DR 事件的时候
An important aspect of a DR failover that often goes overlooked is
经常忽略的 DR 故障转移的重要方面是
deciding when an ongoing incident is actually bad enough to start a DR failover.
确定当前事件的实际情况是否足够差 以启动 DR 故障转移
When an incident starts,
当事件发生时
you expect that it will resolve shortly.
你预期很快就会解决
When it doesn't, at what point do you implement your disaster recovery plan?
如果没有 您在什么时候实施灾难恢复计划?
The consideration is how long does it take to recover in your DR location,
需要考虑的是在您的 DR 位置恢复多久
and how long is your RTO? Who decides?
你的 RTO是多久 谁决定
This is a pretty major decision that will likely have repercussions. Who makes the call?
这是一个相当重大的决定 可能会产生影响  谁打来的
The engineer on call,
电话里的工程师
the engineering manager, the VP, CTO, CEO?
工程经理 副总裁  CTO   CEO?
You should establish the preferred order of decision-makers.
您应该建立决策制定者的首选顺序
Make sure that it's documented and that anyone who
确保记录在案
is on the list knows that they are on the list.
名单上的人知道他们在名单上
You don't want to surprise the CEO in the middle of the night and ask if you should
你不想在半夜惊喜 CEO  问你是否应该
institute a DR failover if they don't know what that means.
如果他们不知道这意味着什么 就会进行 DR 故障转移
There are several types of DR planning.
DR 规划有多种类型
Cold standby means that you have all the data you need in your DR location,
冷备用表示您在 DR 位置拥有所需的所有数据
but every server and database will need to be spun up in order to perform a DR recovery.
但每个服务器和数据库都需要进行旋转 才能执行 DR 恢复
A pilot light plan would always have
一个试验计划
a bare minimum of some of the things always in your DR environment.
在您的 DR 环境中始终至少有一些内容
This can be things like an active read replica of a database in your DR environment.
这可能是 DR 环境中数据库的活动读副本
A warm standby scenario would have
热备用方案将具有
the minimum amount of everything running in your DR region.
在您的 DR 区域中运行的最低数量
So you would have databases and perhaps
所以你会有数据库
one of each server type always running in your DR region.
每个服务器类型都在您的 DR 区域中运行
A hot standby would be a complete second environment running at all times,
热备用会是一个完整的第二个环境
ready to be cut over too.
也准备被割断
Of these different types,
在这些不同的类型中
you must decide on the appropriate trade-off
必须作出适当的权衡取舍
between cost of running things in your DR region
在 DR 区域中运行事物的成本之间
and the cost of time spent getting
以及花费的时间
your DR region capable of handling all of your production traffic.
您的 DR 区域可以处理所有生产流量